Lights reduced to swiping left and right.
Scrolling through the void in the pale blue light.
Profiles lined up like a deck of cards.
Laughing at the boredom hiding all our scars.
Notifications chasing through another night.
It's easier to scroll to try to make it right.
Everyone's performing, no one wants the truth.
Chasing validation just to numb our ear.
Swipe left of reality fading into screens Matching with a ghost or another me Connection is a scroll validation hit Propulse in the dark pretending we exist Whoa, whoa, whoa Empty hearts on hold Whoa, whoa, whoa Dopamine so cold
I'm just another pixel in a cynical parade Tapping out confessions to a digital charade Filters on my feelings and the bio is cliche We chase another stranger just to fill the day We never look up from the glare Lost in the feed we share Wasting days in disrepair Do you even care?
Swipe left of reality fading into screens.
Maxing with a ghost or another meme.
Connection is a scroll validation hitch.
Profiles in the dark pretending we exist.
Empty hearts on hold.
Dopamine so cold.